Guide to the Doris Ulmann Photograph Collection ca. 1910-1934 PR 72
New-York Historical Society
- short, straight, graying hair, parted, round eyeglasses, mustache, jacket, tie [Thomas, Henry M., M.D., Clinical Professor of Neurology], 157178 (Item 2040)
- salt and pepper gray hair, mustache, husky, [Fordyce, John A., Professor of Dermatology and Syphilology, Columbia], 157177 (Item 2041)
- salt and pepper gray hair, mustache, husky, seated [Fordyce, John A., Professor of Dermatology and Syphilology, Columbia], 157176 (Item 2042)
  #1116, 1443, 2009, 2041, 2042 same subject; another image of subject in "XXIV Portraits.. ."; mat and mount missing
- older, white/gray hair, longish beard, mustache, in tuxedo, medals or decorations on jacket, holding book or paper, cane, 157175 (Item 2043)
- older, white/gray hair, longish beard, mustache, in tuxedo, medals or decorations on jacket, holding book or paper, cane, 157174 (Item 2044)
- older, white/gray hair, longish beard, mustache, in tuxedo, medals or decorations on jacket, 157173 (Item 2045)
- older, white/gray hair, longish beard, mustache, in leather jacket, leather cap, pipe, looks like a sea captain, 157172 (Item 2046)
- young, dark, smooth hair, parted on side, jacket, tie, holding pipe, looking to side, 157171 (Item 2047)
- gray hair, straight, round eyeglasses, husky, seated, leaning on table, jacket, tie, 157170 (Item 2048)
  #975, 2048, 2278 same subject, mat and mount missing
- gray hair, salt and pepper mustache, husky, seated at desk, round eyeglasses [Finney, John Miller Turpin, M.D., Professor of Clinical Surgery, JHU], 157169 (Item 2049)
  #2049, 2191, 2247, 2248, 2336, 2367, 2368, 2908 same image; subject is in "A Book of Portraits" but not this image; mat and mount missing
- dark jacket, tie [Frost, Robert], 157168 (Item 2050)
  #1183, 1249, 1250, 1519, 1525, 2050, 2293 same subject, mat and mount missing
- seated outside a cabin, dark thick hair, mustache, muscular, light colored shirt, sleeves rolled up, striped pants, holding a tool(?) or musical instrument (?), 157167 (Item 2051)
- old, bushy gray hair, prominent ears, round eyeglasses, jacket, tie, playing a fiddle or violin, 157166 (Item 2052)
- seated outside a cabin, felt hat, v-neck cardigan, long nose, 157165 (Item 2053)
- balding, salt and pepper hair, seated, dark suit, tie, handkerchief in pocket, dark eyebrows, scowling, 157164 (Item 2054)
  #2054-2056 same subject, mat and mount missing
- balding, salt and pepper hair, seated, dark suit, tie, handkerchief in pocket, dark eyebrows, smiling, 157163 (Item 2055)
- balding, salt and pepper hair, seated, dark suit, tie, handkerchief in pocket, dark eyebrows, smiling, 157162 (Item 2056)
- round dark rimmed eyeglasses, dark strait thinning hair, suit, tie, seated with book, 157161 (Item 2057)
- round dark rimmed eyeglasses, dark strait thinning hair, suit, tie, seated, head on arm, 157160 (Item 2058)
- round dark rimmed eyeglasses, dark strait thinning hair, suit, tie, seated at desk, 157159 (Item 2059)
- round dark rimmed eyeglasses, dark strait thinning hair, suit, tie, seated with book, 157158 (Item 2060)
- round dark rimmed eyeglasses, dark strait thinning hair, suit, tie, seated with book, 157157 (Item 2061)
- salt and pepper hair, straight, parted, older, mustache, suit, high collared shirt, tie [Goodnow, Frank Johnson, LL.D., President of the University, Johns Hopkins University], 157156 (Item 2062)
  #2062, 2400, 2401 same subject, subject is in "A Book of Portraits.. .", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- medium dark curly hair, seated, jacket, vest, high collared shirt, watch chain [Coy, George J., Registrar of the Medical Department, Johns Hopkins University], 157155 (Item 2063)
- medium dark curly hair, seated, jacket, vest, high collared shirt, watch chain [Coy, George J., Registrar of the Medical Department, Johns Hopkins University], 157154 (Item 2064)
- dark thinning hair, salt and pepper mustache and pointy beard, seated with pencil and pad (?), jacket, vest, tie [Meyer, Adolf, M.S., LL.D., Professor of Psychiatry, Johns Hopkins University], 157153 (Item 2065)
  2065, 2067, 2388, 2389 same subject, subject is in "A Book of Portraits.. .", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- older, balding, salt and pepper hair, mustache, round eyeglasses, suit, high collar, standing, chin in hand, looking pensive, laboratory equipment in background [Abel, John J., M.D., Sc. D., Professor of Pharmacology, JHU], 157152 (Item 2066)
  #2066, 2397, 2396 same subject, subject is in "A Book of Portraits.. .", but not this image
- dark thinning hair, salt and pepper mustache and pointy beard, seated with pencil and pad (?), jacket, vest, tie [Meyer, Adolf, M.S., LL.D., Professor of Psychiatry, Johns Hopkins University], 157151 (Item 2067)
  2065, 2067 same subject, subject is in "A Book of Portraits.. .", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- thinning medium light straight hair, mustache, young, jacket, vest, tie, holding book, 157150 (Item 2068)
  JHU?, mat and mount missing
- at table with papers, gray suit, striped shirt, tie [Johnson, James Weldon poet, diplomat, songwriter, and anthologist of black culture], 157149 (Item 2069)
- salt and pepper straight hair, parted on side, mustache, pince nez eyeglasses, striped jacket, striped tie, striped shirt, high collar, 157148 (Item 2070)
  #2070, 2071 same subject, mat and mount missing
- salt and pepper straight hair, parted on side, mustache, pince nez eyeglasses, striped jacket, striped tie, striped shirt, high collar, seated with book, wall hanging or illustration in background, 157147 (Item 2071)
- dark, curly hair, balding a little, round eyeglasses, suit, tie, vest, seated, 157146 (Item 2072)
- balding, white hair, mustache, jowls, scowling, dark suit, vest, tie, holding pencil, ring on left pinky, 157145 (Item 2073)
- white hair, balding a little, but thick, mustache, beard, jacket, tie, holding rolled papers, seated in garden, 157144 (Item 2074)
- thin, straight white hair, clean shaven square face, stock, seated on studio chair with carved turned arms, striped suit, vest, tie, watch chain, 157143 (Item 2075)
- thin, almost bald, short white or gray hair, seated, suit, striped tie, 157142 (Item 2076)
- bald, white mustache, beard trimmed very small, dark suit, vest, tie, seated with open book, 157141 (Item 2077)
- dark straight thick hair, young, suit, vest, tie, button down collar on shirt, seated with pipe and papers (manuscript?) [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157140 (Item 2078)
  #1229-1231, 2078, 2079 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. ." but not this image, mat and mount missing
- dark straight thick hair, young, suit, vest, tie, button down collar on shirt, seated with pipe and papers (manuscript?) [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157139 (Item 2079)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, seated, double breasted suit, tie [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157138 (Item 2080)
  #2080-2096, 2098 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery of American Editors", but not this image; mat and mount missing
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, tie, seated sideways pointing (as if scolding) at a sculpture/figurines two women nude, embracing, a Vanity Fair cover hangs on curtain in background [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157137 (Item 2081)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, tie, standing pointing (as if scolding) at a sculpture/figurines two women nude, embracing, a Vanity Fair cover hangs on curtain in background [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157136 (Item 2082)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, tie, seated, staring into camera [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157135 (Item 2083)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157134 (Item 2084)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157133 (Item 2085)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157132 (Item 2086)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated with small open book and pencil [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157131 (Item 2087)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157130 (Item 2088)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated with papers or manuscripts holding pencil [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157129 (Item 2089)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated, arms/hands crossed on lap, legs crossed [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157128 (Item 2090)
  #2080-2096, 2098 same subject; mat and mount missing
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated at table with small open book [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157127 (Item 2091)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated at table with small open book and pencil [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157126 (Item 2092)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated staring straight at camera [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157125 (Item 2093)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated with small book [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157124 (Item 2094)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated staring straight into camera [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157123 (Item 2095)
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated with pencil and pile of papers or manuscripts [Crowninshield, Frank, Editor, Vanity Fair], 157122 (Item 2096)
- balding, medium dark hair, stout, seated, suit, vest, tie, holding magazine, monocle [Shipman, Louis Evan, Editor, Life], 157121 (Item 2097)
  #2097, 2163, 3015 same subject; subject is in "A Portrait Gallery of American Editors", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- straight, short, thick white hair, parted on side, double breasted suit, seated with small book [Shipman, Louis Evan, Editor, Life], 157120 (Item 2098)
- bald, dark eyebrows, mustache, little beard, jacket, vest, tie, seated with cigar [Cullen, Thomas Stephen, M.B., Professor of Clinical Gynecology], 157119 (Item 2099)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated with book, 157118 (Item 2100)
  #1326, 1444, 1888, 1889, 1914-1918, 2100-2108 same subject; mat and mount missing
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated with book, 157117 (Item 2101)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated, 157116 (Item 2102)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated with book, 157115 (Item 2103)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated, wearing hat, 157114 (Item 2104)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated, wearing hat, 157113 (Item 2105)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated, wearing hat, 157112 (Item 2106)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated, wearing hat, arms crossed on chest, 157111 (Item 2107)
- white mustache, bald, military uniform, decorations, seated, wearing hat, hands clasped in lap, 157110 (Item 2108)
- dark hair, bald, dark eyebrows, not old, gray suit, tie, pince nez eyeglasses, standing in front of cabinet of flat-file-like drawers, anatomical models (?) on top of cabinet of part of human brain?, 157109 (Item 2109)
  not JHU, not Columbia
- bald, white/white mustache, thick rimmed and thick lenses round eyeglasses, seated, suit, vest, tie [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157108 (Item 2110)
  #2110-2113, 2713, 2752, 2929 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. .", but not this image; mat and mount missing
- bald, white/white mustache, thick rimmed and thick lenses round eyeglasses, seated, suit, vest, tie, at desk or table with books [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157107 (Item 2111)
- bald, white/white mustache, thick rimmed and thick lenses round eyeglasses, seated, suit, vest, tie, at desk or table with books [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157106 (Item 2112)
- bald, white/white mustache, thick rimmed and thick lenses round eyeglasses, seated, suit, vest, tie, at desk or table with books [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157105 (Item 2113)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157104 (Item 2114)
  #2114-2124, 2996 same subject; subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. ." but not this image; mat and mount missing
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157103 (Item 2115)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated with copy of Hearst International magazine [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157102 (Item 2116)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, chin on hand [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157101 (Item 2117)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157100 (Item 2118)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, chin in hand [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157099 (Item 2119)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated leaning forward [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157098 (Item 2120)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated leaning forward [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157097 (Item 2121)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated with Hearst International magazine [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157096 (Item 2122)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated with cigarette [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157095 (Item 2123)
- medium dark straight thin hair, a little disheveled, bags under eyes, deep smile lines, cleft chin, suit, vest, tie, seated with Hearst International magazine, smiling [Hapgood, Norman, Editor, Hearst International], 157094 (Item 2124)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, with book, at desk [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157093 (Item 2125)
  #1073, 1286-1288, 2125-2134, 2999 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery of Am. Ed.", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, with book, at desk [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157092 (Item 2126)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, at desk with books, papers [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157091 (Item 2127)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157090 (Item 2128)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, at desk with books, papers [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157089 (Item 2129)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157088 (Item 2130)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, at desk with books, papers [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157087 (Item 2131)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, at desk writing [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157086 (Item 2132)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, seated [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157085 (Item 2133)
- flower in lapel, dark hair, curly, small mustache, seated with illustrated book in front of bookshelf [Wright, Richardson Little, Editor, House and Garden, b. 1886], 157084 (Item 2134)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157083 (Item 2135)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157082 (Item 2136)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157081 (Item 2137)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157080 (Item 2138)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157079 (Item 2139)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157078 (Item 2140)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157077 (Item 2141)
- bald, dark round eyeglasses, double breasted jacket [Wells, Thomas B., Editor, Harper's Magazine], 157076 (Item 2142)
  #1990, 2135-2142, 2746-2751, 2937 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. .", but not this image; mat and mount missing
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157075 (Item 2143)
  #1229-1231, 2143-2152, 2724, 2984 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. ." but not this image
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157074 (Item 2144)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157073 (Item 2145)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157072 (Item 2146)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157071 (Item 2147)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157070 (Item 2148)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157069 (Item 2149)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157068 (Item 2150)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157067 (Item 2151)
- young middle age, straight medium dark hair, suit jacket with breast pockets on the outside, vest, tie [Walsh, Richard J., editor, Collier's], 157066 (Item 2152)
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157065 (Item 2153)
  #2153-2159 same subject; subject is in "A Portrait Gallery.. .", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157064 (Item 2154)
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157063 (Item 2155)
  #2153-2159 same subject; mat and mount missing
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157062 (Item 2156)
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157061 (Item 2157)
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157060 (Item 2158)
- middle aged, balding, gray mustache, round eyeglasses, somewhat stout, suit, tie, vest [Hendrick, Burton Jesse, Editor, The World's Work], 157059 (Item 2159)
- middle aged, balding, medium dark hair, suit, bow tie, vest, seated with pencil, pad, book, 157058 (Item 2160)
  #2160-2162 same subject, mat and mount missing
- middle aged, balding, medium dark hair, suit, bow tie, vest, 157057 (Item 2161)
- middle aged, balding, medium dark hair, suit, bow tie, vest, 157056 (Item 2162)
- balding, medium dark hair, stout, seated, suit, vest, tie, monocle [Shipman, Louis Evan, Editor, Life], 157055 (Item 2163)
  #2097, 2163, 3015 same subject; mat and mount missing
- middle aged, receding hair line, medium dark hair, stout, suit, vest, tie, pipe in mouth, 157054 (Item 2164)
  #2164-2166 same subject, mat and mount missing
- middle aged, receding hair line, medium dark hair, stout, suit, vest, tie, 157053 (Item 2165)
- middle aged, receding hair line, medium dark hair, stout, suit, vest, tie, pipe in mouth, 157052 (Item 2166)
- young, thick dark straight unruly hair, seated, suit vest, tie, one hand on table, on hand touching his neck [Mumford, Lewis, American writer and critic], 157051 (Item 2167)
  #1182, 2168, 2235 same subject; mat and mount missing
- middle aged, in lab coat, receding hairline, tie, seated at bench with beakers, chin resting on hand [Howland, John, M.D., Professor of Pediatrics, JHU], 157050 (Item 2168)
- balding, straight medium dark hair, middle aged, mustache, pince nez eyeglasses, striped suit, tie, in profile, seated at desk with pen writing, 157049 (Item 2169)
- balding, straight medium dark hair, middle aged, mustache, pince nez eyeglasses, striped suit, tie, 3/4 profile, seated at desk reading newspaper, 157048 (Item 2170)
- old, white/gray hair, longish beard, mustache, in tuxedo, medals or decorations on jacket, holding a cigarette, 157047 (Item 2171)
- old, white/gray hair, longish beard, mustache, in leather zipped vest, waterproof canvas jacket, cap, with pipe, looking like a sea captain, actor?, 157046 (Item 2172)
- young, very thin medium dark hair, balding, mustache, round dark rimmed eyeglasses, suit, vest, tie, seated at desk or table with open book, pen in hand as if signing, 157045 (Item 2173)
  #2173, 2174, 2202, 2340 same subject; mat and mount missing
- young, very thin medium dark hair, balding, mustache, round dark rimmed eyeglasses, suit, vest, tie, seated slouched in upholstered chair, wavy wallpaper in background, 157044 (Item 2174)
- middle aged, thinning medium dark colored straight hair, parted in middle, salt and pepper beard and mustache, bags under his eyes [Bridges, Robert, Editor, Scribner's], 157043 (Item 2175)
  #2175-2190, 2759, 2995 same subject, subject is in "A Portrait Gallery of American Editors", but not this image, mat and mount missing
- middle aged, thinning medium dark colored straight hair, parted in middle, salt and pepper beard and mustache, bags under his eyes [Bridges, Robert, Editor, Scribner's], 157042 (Item 2176)